{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40133/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40133,"taskName":"Asphalt Shingle Roofing - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace an Asphalt Shingle Roof","xmTaskDescriptor":"Asphalt Roofing Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":3502,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Asphalt Roofing Shingles replacement gaf","textMessagingName":"Inst Asphalt Roof","rolloverLongDesc":"Asphalt shingles are sometimes fiberglass reinforced \u0026 are the most common roofing material in the U.S. They come in 1x3 foot sections that are nailed or stapled to the roof in overlapping rows. The panels are a bit like heavily tarred felt with a sandy surface on top \u0026 come in many colors, though gray \u0026 tan are most common.","rolloverShortDesc":"The most common type of shingle roof.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace an Asphalt Shingle Roof.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Asphalt Shingle \u0026 Roof Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Asphalt Shingles","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Asphalt Shingle Roof Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Asphalt Shingle Roofing - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Asphalt Shingle Roofing Project","urlName":"Asphalt-Shingle-Roofing-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Asphalt Roof \u0026 Shingle Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Cost Info, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Asphalt,Roofing,Shingles,replacement,gaf,exterior,siding,Roofers,roof,fiberglass,tar","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":444,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"taskHeader":"Asphalt Roofing Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40133/":{"taskOID":40133,"originalTaskOID":40133,"setID":444,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160806,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features for Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160807,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160806,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features for Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160807,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376523369pwspr015F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}